A Guide to the Clifton A. Woodrum Papers, 1979-1999
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Numerical files, 1979-1999., Extent: 33.3 cu. ft. (74 boxes) (Box 1-74)
  - 14. Elections, State Board.
    - [14.002] Campaign files (contribution and expenditure forms), 1979-1988. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - [14.004] State Board of Elections general correspondence 1986-1991. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - [14.007] Conflict of interest 1986. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - [14.008] Proposed constitutional amendments public information brochure, 1990. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - [14.008-A] Constitutional amendments, 1998. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - [14.010] Campaign finance reform, ethics, etc., 1992. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 17. General Services, Dept. of
    - [17.001-A] Shenandoah Elevator Company, 1990-1991. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - [17.001-B] State carpet, 1993. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - [17.002] Virginia's Mapping Office, 1989. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 18. Health, Dept. of.
    - [18.001] Communicable diseases AIDS, 1987-1990. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - [18.002] Sewage handling and disposal regulations, 1987-1989. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - [18.003] Health care reforms general, 1987-1991. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - [18.003-A] Health care reform, 1992. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - [18.003-B] Health care provider tax, 1992. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - [18.004] Smoking issues, 1987-1990. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - [18.004-A] H.B. 430 Clean Indoor Air Act, 1989. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - [18.005] H.B. 1650, 1651 Asbestos bill, 1989. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - [18.005] H.B. 1650, 1651 Asbestos bill, 1989. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - [18.005] H.B. 1650, 1651 Asbestos bill, 1989. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - [18.005] H.B. 1650, 1651 Asbestos bill, 1989. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - [18.005] H.B. 1650, 1651 Asbestos bill, 1989. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - [18.005] H.B. 1650, 1651 Asbestos bill, 1989. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - [18.005-A] H.B. 179 Asbestos bill, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - [18.005-A(1)] H.B. 277 State agencies contracts for asbestos projects, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - [18.005-A(2)] H.B. 407 Asbestos contractors, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - [18.006] Alzheimer's disease, 1988. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - [18.006-A] Alzheimer's disease and disorder registry, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - [18.007] Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1988-1992. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - [18.007-B] Blue Cross/Blue Shield- First Option, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - [18.007-C] Blue Cross/Blue Shield - Convert to non-stock, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - [18.007-E] Blue Cross/Blue Shield - General correspondence, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - [18.007-F] Blue Cross/Blue Shield - Calculation of patient co-payments, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - [18.008] Hazardous material, 1987-1988. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - [18.009] WIC Program, 1988. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - [18.010] General correspondence, 1987-1989. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - [18.010] General correspondence,, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - [18.011] Certificate of need, 1988-1991. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - [18.012-B] S.B. 502 Bottle bill, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - [18.013] H.B. 23 Surrogacy, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - [18.014] Acid rain, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - [18.015] Brown lung, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - [18.017] Improper closure of pollution control facilities, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - [18.018] Trauma triage regulation, 1996-1997. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - [18.023] S.B. 1174 End of life decisions, 1999. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - [18.024] Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1999. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 19. Health Regulatory Board, Dept. of
    - [19.001] Dentistry, 1987. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - [19.001-A] Dental hygienists, 1987. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - [19.003] State Board of Nursing, 1985-1990. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - [19.004] Optometrists, 1986-1987. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - [19.008] Therapeutic Drug Bill, 1988. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - [19.009] Medicaid- General correspondence, 1998. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - [19.009] Medicaid- General correspondence, 1998. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - [19.010] Dr. James Holman certification, 1989. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - 20. Joint Legislative Audit Review Commission.
    - [20.001] Amendments, 1990-1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - [20.002] S.B. 248 Funding of Constitutional officers, 1990. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - 21. Housing and Community Development.
    - [21.001] Housing in urban areas, 1986-1987. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - [21.001] Housing in urban areas, 1986-1987. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - [21.001] Housing in urban areas, 1986-1987. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - [21.001] Housing in urban areas, 1986-1987. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - [21.002] Fair Housing Law, 1987-1988. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - [21.003] Urban Enterprise Zone, 1983-1985. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - [21.003-A] Urban Enterprise Zone, 1994. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - [21.004] H.B. 532 Eminent Domain, 1988. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - [21.005] Virginia Housing Partnership Fund, 1988-1990. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - [21.006] Housing and community development- General correspondence, 1988-1990. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - [21.007] VHDA, 1990. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 22. Industrial Commission.
    - [22.001] H.B. 536 Workers Compensation, 1984-1990. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - [22.001-A] Workers Compensation, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - [22.001-B] Workers Compensation, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - [22.001-C] S.B. 929 False Statements in Awards Class 1 Misdemeanor, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - [22.001-D] Va. Workers Compensation Commissioner vacancy, 1993-1994. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - [22.001-F] Criminal Injuries Compensation Fund, 1998. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - 23. Information Technology.
    - [23.001] Computer services, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - [23.002] Telecommunication division, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - 24. Mental Health and Mental Retardation.
    - [24.001] General correspondence, 1991. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - [24.002] Mental Health Equity Inc., 1991. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - 25. Mines, Minerals and Energy.
    - [25.002] General correspondence, 1989. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - 26. Motor Vehicles, Dept. of
    - [26.001] Habitual offenders, 1986-1993. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - [26.002] Drunk driving, 1982-1989. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - [26.003] VASAP, 1984-1986. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - [26.004] Speed limit increase, 1988. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - [26.005] Vehicular homicide/Involuntary manslaughter, nd. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - [26.006] H.B. 397 Failure to stop, 1988. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - [26.007] General Assembly, 1988-1990. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - [26.008] H.B. 478 Lemon law, Warranty Enforcement, 1988. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - [26.009] Bus speed limit increase, 1989. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - [26.010] Commercial drivers' license, 1989-1990. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - [26.011] H.J.R. 69 Motor vehicle repair businesses, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - [26.012] H.B. 687 Vehicle inspection expiration, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - [26.013] Mothers Against Drunk Driving, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - 28. Virginia Supplemental Retirement System
    - [28.001] Virginia Retirement system, 1990-1992. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - [28.001] Virginia Retirement system, 1990-1992. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - [28.002] Irwin Holtzman, 1986. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - [28.003] Taxation of Government Retirees, 1989. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - [28.003] Taxation of Government Retirees, 1989. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - [28.003-A] Taxation of Government Retirees, 1990. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - [28.003-B] Taxation of Government Retirees, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - [28.003-D] H.B. 1767 Board of Trustees, Virginia Retirement System, 1993. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - [28.003-E] Federal retirees settlement of pension, 1994. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - [28.003-G] Joint Subcommittee Studying Capital Access and Business Financing, 1996. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - [28.004] H.B. 180 Retirement benefits for Dept. ABC, 1990. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - [28.006] Potomac Yard Stadium (Alexandria, VA)- Against, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - [28.006] Potomac Yard Stadium (Alexandria, VA)- Against, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - [28.006] Potomac Yard Stadium (Alexandria, VA)- For, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - [28.006] Virginia Retirement Stadium Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - [28.006] Virginia Retirement Stadium Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - [28.006] Virginia Retirement Stadium Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - [28.006] Virginia Retirement Stadium Redskin Stadium, 1992. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 29. Center in the Square
    - [29.003] Roanoke Valley Science Museum appropriations, 1989. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - 30. Secretary of the Commonwealth
    - [30.008] Lobbyist list, 1994-1995. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 31. Social Services
    - [31.001] Family Service of Roanoke Valley, 1987. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - [31.002] Social Services general correspondence, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - [31.004] H.B. 688 Child support enforcement, 1986-1990. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - [31.004] H.B. 688 Child support enforcement, 1986-1990. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - [31.004] H.B. 688 Child support enforcement, 1986-1990. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - [31.004-A] Non-Custodial Parent Support and Citizens for Justice, 1989. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - [31.005] Planned Parenthood, 1984-1993. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - [31.006] Abortion, 1981-1991. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - [31.006] Abortion, 1981-1991. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - [31.006-A] Abortion issues, 1992. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - [31.006-B] Abortion issues, 1993. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - [31.006-C] Abortion issues, 1993. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - [31.007] Parental consent, 1984-1991. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - [31.007] Parental consent, 1984-1991. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - [31.007-A] Parental consent and notification, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - [31.007-A] Parental consent and notification, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - [31.007-C] Abortion issues, 1994. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - [31.007-D] Abortion issues, 1995. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - [31.008] Virginia Forum- Virginia's Children and Families, 1987. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - [31.009] Adult day care, 1983. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - [31.010] Companion service program, 1987. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - [31.011] Free Clinic of Roanoke Valley, 1986-1988. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - [31.012] Budget allocation for social services, 1987-1991. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - [31.013] Head Start Program, 1996. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - [31.013] Head Start Program, 1996. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - [31.014] United Way of Virginia, 1989. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - [31.015] Freddie Lee Yancey Auxiliary grant, 1989. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - [31.016] Welfare Reform Sub Committee, 1989. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 32. Transportation and Public Safety
    - [32.001] Caboose, 1987-1988. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - [32.002] Valley Metro-Greater Roanoke Transit Company, 1988. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - [32.003] Transportation general correspondence, 1989-1991. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - [32.004] Boating while intoxicated, 1989. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - [32.006] Highways- General correspondence, 1987-1991. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - [32.006] Highways- General correspondence, Transportation taxes, 987-1991. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - [32.006] Highways- General correspondence, Clippings, 1986. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - [32.006] Transportation funding, 1999. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - [32.006-A] Highways- General correspondence, State Route 691, 1991. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - [32.007] Highway- Roanoke, Blacksburg Road, Smart Road, 1989-1993. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - [32.008] Roanoke River Parkway, 1990. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - [32.009] Yokohama Tire Corporation, 1993. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - 33. Visually handicapped
    - [32.002] Valley Metro Greater Roanoke Transit Company, 1987-1989. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - 34. War veterans
    - [34.001] Vietnam Veterans, 1984-1989. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - [34.002] Veterans' Cemetery, 1987-1988. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - [34.003] Agent Orange, 1987. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - [34.004] State Veterans' Home, 1988-1989. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - [34.005] General- War Veterans Claim, 1988-1993. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - [34.006] Veterans' Care Center, 1988-1989. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 35. Water Control Board
    - [35.001] Underground storage tanks, 1986. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - [35.002] State Water Commission, 1988-1990. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - [35.003] Spring Hollow Reservoir, 1987. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - [35.003-B] Water Commission, 1992. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - [35.004] Instream Flow Legislation, 1988-1992. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - [35.005] Alleghany Construction Company- Request for Water Control Board Exemption Certificate for Sanitary Landfill, 1988-1989. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - [35.006] Drinking Water Protection Plan, 1990. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - [35.007] Water Chemistry, Inc., 1990. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - [35.008] Chesapeake Bay Preservation Act, 1990-1992. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - [35.010] Town of Fincastle- Safe Drinking Water Act, 1986. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - 36. Women's issues
    - [36.001] Shelter for Battered Women, 1987. (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - [36.002] Jr. League of Roanoke Valley, 1982-1989. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - 37. Woodrum General Files
    - [37.002] Constituent Services, Miscellaneous 1988-1999. (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - [37.002] Constituent Services, Miscellaneous, 1988-1999. (Box 34)
    - [37.005] Constituent Services, Nominations and Recommendations, 1988-1999. (Box 34, Folder 34-50)
    - [37.008] Constituent Services, Resolutions, 1996. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - [37.009] Constituent Services, Invitation and replies, 1986-1990. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - [37.013] Constituent Services, General correspondence, 1989. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - [37.013] Constituent Services, General correspondence, 1989. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - [37.013] Constituent Services, General correspondence, 1990. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - [37.013] Constituent Services, General correspondence, 1991. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - [37.013] Constituent Services, General correspondence, 1991-1993. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - [37.014] Bills and receipts, 1988-1993. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - [37.015] List of Committee and Subcommittee assignments, 1988-1989. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - [37.016] S.J.R. 45 State Grievance Procedure, 1988-1990. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - [37.017] H.J.R. 100 Freedom of Information Act, Correspondence, 1988-1990. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - [37.017] H.J.R. 100 Freedom of Information Act, 1988-1990. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - [37.017] H.J.R. 100 Freedom of Information Act, 1988-1990. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - [37.017] H.J.R. 100 Freedom of Information Act, 1988-1990. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - [37.017] H.J.R. 100 Freedom of Information Act, 1988-1990. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - [37.017-A] H.J.R. 100 Freedom of Information Act,, 1988-1990. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - [37.017-A1] H.B. 690 Code of Virginia and Virginia Freedom of Information Act, 1990. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - [37.018] Tours, School groups, 1988-1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - [37.019] Boyd Graves Conference, 1988-1992. (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - [37.021] Interim Studies - Joint Subcommittee Study Resolutions and Commission, 1990. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - [37.022] Bristol-Myers- Squibb Company (stock), 1990. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - [37.024] Student requests for information about government, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - [37.026] 1-800 Comments, 1996. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - [37.027] Thank you letters from constituents, 1995. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - [37.028] Outgoing mail for Woodrum, 1995. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - [37.028] Outgoing mail for Woodrum, 1995. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - [37.028] Outgoing mail for Woodrum, 1995. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - [37.028] Outgoing mail for Woodrum, 1995. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 38. Democratic Party
    - [38.001] General correspondence, 1983-1989. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - [38.001] General correspondence, 1983-1989. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - [38.001] General correspondence, 1983-1989. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - [38.001] General correspondence, 1983-1989. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - [38.001] General correspondence, 1983-1989. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - [38.003] Democratic Party Plan, Rules, Etc., 1985-1989. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - [38.004-A] Nominating Process, Filing, Etc., 1991. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - [38.005] National Conventions, 1988. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - [38.007] Sixth Congressional District (Temporary Rules, Etc.), 1982-1985. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - [38.008] Virginia Democratic Convention (Rules Comm.), 1985-1989. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - [38.008] Virginia Democratic Convention (Rules Comm.), 1985-1989. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - [38.009] Democratic Caucus, 1983-1991. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - [38.009] Democratic Caucus, 1983-1991. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - [38.009] Democratic Caucus, 1983-1991. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - [38.009] Democratic Caucus, 1983-1991. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - [38.009-B] Annual Speaker's Golf Tournament, 1984-1989. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - [38.009-B] Annual Speaker's Golf Tournament, 1984-1989. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - [38.009-B(1)] Annual Speaker's Golf Tournament, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - [38.009-B(2)] Annual Speaker's Golf Tournament, 1990. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - [38.009-B(3)] The Joint Caucus Gala, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - [38.009-B(5)] Annual Speaker's Golf Tournament, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - [38.009-B(6)] The Joint Caucus Gala, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - [38.009-B(7)] Annual Speaker's Golf Tournament, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - [38.009-C] General correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - [38.009-D] Delegate Development, 1987-1989. (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - [38.010] Southern Legislative Conference, 1988-1991. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - 39. Woodrum Campaign
    - [39.001] Availability meetings, 1983-1986. (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - [39.002] Commendation letters, 1985-1992. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - [39.002] Commendation letters, 1985-1992. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - [39.004] Questionnaires, 1987-1989. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - [39.004-A] Questionnaires, 1991. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - [39.004-C] Questionnaires, 1993. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - [39.005] Re-election campaign, 1987. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - [39.005] Re-election campaign, 1987. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - [39.005] Re-election campaign, 1987. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - [39.005] Re-election campaign, 1987. (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - [39.018] Contributions received, 1992-1993. (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - [39.018-A] Contributions given, 1992-1993. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - [39.018-B] Contributions rejected, 1992-1993. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - [39.018-C] Woodrum, Cranwell and Thomas Roast, 1993. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - [39.020] Frank Hargrove letter to editor (Richmond Times Dispatch), 1994. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 40. Campaigns of others
    - [40.001] James R. Olin correspondence, 1984-1985. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - [40.003] Mary Sue Terry for Governor, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - [40.005] James M. Young Va. House of Delegates campaign, 1987. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - [40.006] General campaign correspondence, 1988-1992. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - [40.013] Jerry Wood Va. House of Delegates campaign, 1993. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - [40.016] Mark Earley Attorney General, 1998-1999. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - [40.019] Gene Marrano Roanoke County Board of Supervisors campaign, 1999. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 41. Voter registration
    - [41.001] Statewide voter registration, 1984-1988. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - [41.001] Statewide voter registration, 1984-1988. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - 42. Roanoke City
    - [42.002] Roanoke City Legislative Program, 1984-1988. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - [42.002] Roanoke City Legislative Program, 1984-1988. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - [42.002-A] Roanoke City Legislative Program, 1990-1991. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - [42.002-A] Roanoke City Legislative Program, 1990-1991. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - [42.002-B] Trade center, 1987-1988. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - [42.002-C] City of Roanoke resolutions, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - [42.002-D] Roanoke City Legislative Program, 1992. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - [42.002-E] Roanoke City Legislative Program, 1993. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - [42.002-F] Roanoke City Legislative Issues, 1994. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - [42.002-F] Roanoke City Legislative Issues, 1996-1997. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - [42.002-G] Roanoke City attorney and city clerk and Roanoke County clerk, 1995. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - [42.003] Henry street project, 1986. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - [42.004] Roanoke City general correspondence, 1983-1991. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - [42.004] Roanoke City general correspondence, 1983-1991. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - [42.004] Roanoke City general correspondence, 1983-1991. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - [42.005] Roanoke Valley Council of Community Services, 1986-1990. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - [42.005-A] S.B. 201 Guardianship study, 1988. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - [42.006-A] TAP (Total Action against Poverty) General correspondence, 1992. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - [42.006-B] TAP requests, 1989. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - [42.006-D] TAP requests, 1988. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - [42.006-E] TAP requests, 1990. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - [42.006-E(1)] CHIP, 1996. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - [42.006-F] Community action services, 1987-1991. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - [42.006-G] Project Discovery, 1984-1995. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - [42.006-H] Virginia Cares, 1993. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - [42.006-I] Exemption from real estate taxes, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - [42.006-J] TAP Funding letters from constituents, 1990. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - [42.006-K] TAP Housing Crest Hill, 1991. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - [42.006-L] TAP's OPTS, 1996. (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - [42.007] Virginia transportation museum budget requests, 1988. (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - [42.008] Roanoke city school, 1989. (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - [42.008-A] Roanoke city school funding, 1986-1989. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - [42.008-B] Education funding letters, 1988. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - [42.008-C] Education funding letters, 1989. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - [42.008-E] Roanoke city funding, 1991. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - [42.008-G] Roanoke city funding, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - [42.009] Roanoke city jail, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - [42.009] Roanoke city jail, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - [42.009] Roanoke city jail, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - [42.009] Roanoke city jail, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - [42.009] Roanoke city jail, 1993. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - [42.010] Consolidation of City and County (Roanoke), 1990. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - [42.010] Consolidation of City and County (Roanoke), 1990. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - [42.010] Consolidation of City and County (Roanoke), 1990. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - [42.010] Consolidation of City and County (Roanoke), 1990. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - [42.010] Consolidation of City and County (Roanoke), 1990. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - [42.010] Consolidation of City and County (Roanoke), Clippings, 1990. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - [42.011] Roanoke Civic Center, 1989. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - [42.012] Roanoke City unfunded mandates, 1993. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - [42.012-A] Roanoke County Resolution Elimination of Unfunded Mandates, 1993. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - [42.013] Flood control, 1989. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - [42.014] Clerk's office- pay increase, 1989. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - [42.015] Hotel Roanoke, 1991-1997. (Box 49, Folder 1)